(
"ai_sub_version": "1.10.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
Glitter of Love
新曲のお披露目あり！
New song reveal!
ポルカのライブ過去最多 ホロメンゲスト10名
A record 10 Hololive members guesting in Polka's live!
Glitter of Love
1, 2, 3, 4!
遥か空 響いてる
Echoing in the distant sky
祈りは
My prayers...
奇跡に
...become a miracle
ETERNAL BLAZE
作詞：水樹奈々
作曲：上松範康(Elements Garden)
ETERNAL BLAZE
Lyrics: Nana Mizuki
Composition: Noriyasu Agematsu (Elements Garden)
真紅の蒼に溶けて
Melting into the crimson blue
流れてく 涙の粒
Teardrops flow away
迷いなく 包み込む
Enveloping without hesitation
ぬくもりに出会った
I met a certain warmth
真っ白な雪のように
Like the pure white snow
どこまでも 素直な言葉
Honest words reaching everywhere
鉄の羽根 纏った
Clad in wings of steel
僕を動かしてく
They keep me moving forward
傷つくたびに 優しくなれる
Every time I'm hurt, I can become kinder
君のその笑顔だけ 守り抜きたい
I want to protect only your smile
願いはひとつ
That is my one and only wish
時を越え 刻まれた
Carved across time
悲しみの記憶
Memories of sadness
真っ直ぐに 受け止める
Accepting them head-on
君は光の戦士
You are a warrior of light
あの日 胸に灯った
Lit in my heart that day
永遠の炎
The eternal flame
深い闇 解き放って
Releasing the deep darkness
自由の扉 開いてく
I'll open the door to freedom
強く 果てない 未来へ
Toward a strong, endless future
蒼い翠の月に
On the pale green moon
映し出す 心の影
The shadow of my heart is reflected
寂しげに つぶやいた
I lonely whispered...
君のそばにいたい
I want to be by your side
真実と 向き合うこと
To face the truth
教えてくれた勇気は
The courage you taught me
僕を 駆け巡って
Courses through me
夢に目覚めてゆく
And I awaken to a dream
触れ合う気持ち 離れないように
So our touching feelings don't drift apart
しっかりと 抱きしめて 確かな想い
Hold me tight, and I'll carry through
貫いてゆく
These certain feelings
銀の海に 隠した
Hidden in the silver sea
空白のページ
A blank page
君だけが 知っている
Only you know the truth
本当の僕を見せて
Show me the real me
吹き荒れる 切なさに
From the raging heartache
生まれゆく誓い
A vow is born
もう何も 怖くはない
I'm not afraid of anything anymore
結んだ視線 そらさずに
Without averting our locked gaze
大切な『今』はじめる
I'll start this precious 'now'
君が君で いられる場所 幻にされないように
So the place where you can be yourself isn't lost
消えない雨の 苦しみも 鍵を壊して ぶつけてよ
Throw the suffering of the unceasing rain at me
隣に いるから 全てを信じて
Believe in everything, because I'm by your side
時を越え 刻まれた
Carved across time
悲しみの記憶
Memories of sadness
真っ直ぐに 受け止める
Accepting them head-on
君は光の戦士
You are a warrior of light
あの日 胸に灯った
Lit in my heart that day
永遠の炎
The eternal flame
深い闇...
Deep darkness...
解き放って
Set it free
自由の扉 開いてく
Opening the door of freedom
強く果てない未来へ
Toward a strong, endless future
そう今ここから 始まる
Yes, it starts now from here
お待たせみんな！
Everyone, thanks for waiting!
今年もポルカの誕生日が始まったー！
Polka's birthday has begun again this year!
タイトルは、かっこいい、Glitter of Love！
The title is the cool "Glitter of Love"!
というわけで、ハッシュタグはこちら！
So, here's the hashtag!
#尾丸ポルカ生誕祭2026
#OmaruPolkaSeitansai2026
でいっぱい、いっぱい呟いてね！
Tweet lots and lots with it!
はい！
Yes!
いや、今回のテーマがまず、愛と勇気と戦う女の子になってます！
Well, the theme this time is girls who fight with love and courage!
そして、見てくださいこのステージ！
And look at this stage!
えいっ！はぁ〜、すごい広い！
Tada! Wow, it's so huge!
おー、なんとですね、広いんですけど、まずスクリーンが超デカい！大迫力！
Oh, it's huge, but first, the screen is super big! Great impact!
なんとなくいつもの3倍くらい頑張りました！いや、頑張ってもらいました！
I worked about three times harder than usual! Well, I had them work harder for me!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
というわけでですね、ここからゲストの方々がたくさんいらっしゃいます！
So, from here on, many guests will be joining us!
もうホロメンだけなら多分、尾丸ポルカ史上最多のゲスト数だと思っております！
In terms of Hololive members alone, I think it's the largest number of guests in Omaru Polka's history!
それをね、これからノンストップでお送りするので、楽しんでいってください！
We'll be bringing them to you non-stop, so please enjoy!
というわけで、いくぞ！
So, let's go!
遺伝子レベルの
At the genetic level
Independent
絶望も希望も
Embracing both despair
抱いて
and hope
足掻け 命尽きるまで
Struggle until your life ends
星天ギャラクシィクロス
作詞・作曲：上松範康 (Elements Garden)
Housen Galaxy Cross
Lyrics/Composition: Noriyasu Agematsu (Elements Garden)
光と飛沫のKiss
A kiss of light and spray
恋のような
Like love
虹のBirthday
A rainbow birthday
どんな美しき日も
No matter how beautiful the day
何か生まれ 何かが死ぬ
Something is born, and something dies
せめて歌おう I Love You
At least let's sing, I love you
世界がひどい地獄だとしても
Even if the world is a terrible hell
せめて伝えよう I Love You
At least let's convey it, I love you
解放の時は来た
The time for liberation has come
星降る天へと響き跳べ Everybody Song
Ring out and leap to the star-filled heavens, Everybody Song
Stardust
そして奇跡は待つものじゃなくて
And miracles aren't things you wait for
その手で作るものと吠えろ
Shout that they are things you create with your own hands
涙した過去を苦みを
The past you wept through, the bitterness
レクイエムにして
Turn them into a requiem
正々堂々力で
Fair and square, with all your might
輝けFutureを
Shine on, the future
信じ鳴らせ
Believe and ring it out
星天ギャラクシィクロス
Housen Galaxy Cross
独りじゃないことを
That you are not alone
やがて君は知る日のため
For the day you will eventually come to know it
指先伝うアストロ
Astro traveling through your fingertips
分かち合って明日へ向かう
Share it and head toward tomorrow
問わない空に I feel you
To the unquestioning sky, I feel you
自由の魂は鼓動せましない
The soul of freedom will not stop beating
不滅なる夢に I feel you
To the immortal dream, I feel you
魂へと剣を握れ
Grasp the sword for your soul
運命を終焉も断ち切る力で
With the power to cut through fate and the end
そして重ねた友情は...
And the friendship we've built...
不屈の煌めき
An indomitable sparkle
十字となって闇を暴く
Becoming a cross to expose the darkness
駆け抜けた丘には
On the hills we ran through
神様も知らない
Even God doesn't know
歴史が光誇る
History brims with light
My Brave Heart
この絆 星天
This bond, a starry sky
ギャラクシィクロス
Galaxy Cross
月光の翼で
On wings of moonlight
Just dream
熾（おこ）しなる炎で
With a rekindled flame
Big mission
過去背負い戦おう
Let's carry the past and fight
そして奇跡は待つものじゃなくて
And miracles aren't things to wait for
その手で作るものと吠えろ
Roar that they're things you create yourself
何度だって
No matter how many times
立ち上がろうか
Let's stand back up
生ある全の力で
With every ounce of living strength
輝けFuture world
Shine, Future world
信じて進め
Believe and move forward
星天ギャラクシィクロス
Starry Sky Galaxy Cross
Try! Try! Trio Dreams!
Let's Sing! Let's Spin! Let's Dance! Let's Born!
Let's Smile! Let's Fly! Precure!!!
Let's Smile! Let's Fly!
トキメキ 出会い 変わってく 世界
A sparkling heart, a meeting, a changing world
未来 1+1+1は
The future, 1+1+1 is...
無限
...infinity
唇からこぼれる歌は
The song spilling from our lips is...
La-La-Lu-La-Li-La-La
プリズム まぶしい光
Prism, a dazzling light
3人寄れば文殊よりも最高 最強
Three of us together are the absolute best and strongest
はじまる 立ち位置（ポジション） ライブ Enjoy Together
Starting positions, a live performance, let's enjoy together
トキメキ 止まらない ハミング
An unstoppable, exciting humming
Jump & Up!
カンツォーネ
Canzone
Wait & See!
輝くリレーね
A shining relay, isn't it?
好きな 好きな フレーズを
Sing our favorite, favorite phrases
シンフォニー 夢のステージ
A symphony on the stage of dreams
君 あなたの元へ 今夜
To you, to your side, tonight
もっともっと 輝き合えるね
We can shine together more and more
みんな Run! Run! Run!
Everyone, Run! Run! Run!
瞳づくりに いつだって 笑顔 映し合おう
Let's always reflect smiles in each other's eyes
Promise!
君がいるから パワー 生まれるよ 今日も
Because you're here, power is born again today
Try! Try! Trio Dreams!
Let's Sing! Let's Spin! Let's Dance! Let's Born!
Let's Smile! Let's Fly! Precure!!!
Let's Smile! Let's Fly!
一緒だから 感じる Happy
Because we're together, I feel happy
1×1×1は
1×1×1 is...
無敵
...invincible
出し惜しみは なしで 全部 あげたい
I want to give you everything without holding back
La-La-Lu-La-Li-La-La
ハプニングさえも 超 行く ワンダフル
Even the mishaps are beyond wonderful
3人寄れば文殊よりも自慢 自慢
Three of us together—it's our absolute pride and joy
見せるよ きっと 伝説の ライブ アンコール 頂戴
We'll show you a legendary live show, give us an encore
揺るぎ ハート
A steady heart
Pop & Step!
賛成!
Agreed!
All Welcome!
カテゴリーなんて いらないね
We don't need any categories
好きな 好きな 思い切り
Our favorite, favorite, with all our might
シフォンの羽 広げ
Spreading our chiffon wings
ハートの奥の奥へ
Into the deepest parts of our hearts
サンキュー 命は 輝きでできて いるの
Thank you, life is made of pure radiance
Lucky!
ビッグスクリーンも はみ出しちゃう 嬉しい 楽しい
Even the big screen can't contain our happiness and fun
Fabulous!
君を知って 知らない 自分に会えたよ
By knowing you, I've met a side of myself I never knew
Try! Try! Trio Dreams!
やったー！
Yay!
瞳の奥に いつまでも笑顔写し合おう
Let's keep reflecting our smiles into each other's eyes forever.
君がいるからパワー生まれるよ今日も
Because you're here, power is born today as well.
Fly fly トリオドリーミー
Fly fly, Trio Dreamy
Let's beat! Let's beat! Let's dance! Let's burn! Let's smile! Let's fly!
Woo! Free shore!
Let's sing! Let's swing! Let's dance! Let's burn! Let's smile! Let's fly!
Woooo!
Awakening Harmony
暗闇の真ん中 まっすぐな眼差し
In the middle of the darkness, a straightforward gaze.
立ち上がる姿 ちゃんと見ていたよ
I was watching your figure as you stood up.
閉じ込められそうな 心を奮い立たせて
Rousing my heart that felt like it would be trapped.
収まりきらない 輝きを放つ
Releasing a radiance that cannot be contained.
射抜かれた胸の奥 泣きついた眩さ
The brilliance that pierced the depths of my chest and made me cry out.
それだけでもう 自由になる待っていて
With just that, I'll already be free, so wait for me.
取り戻したい 光の世界 その笑顔 勇気
I want to take back the world of light, that smile, courage,
涙 夢 希望の兆し
tears, dreams, the signs of hope.
君と明日を願う内からで生まれる
Our harmony, born from within as we wish for tomorrow with you,
私達のハーモニー 響け
let it ring out.
それでも暗闇は 訪れてしまうもの
Even so, darkness is something that will eventually visit.
惑わされないで 君は君だから
Don't be led astray, because you are you.
私が得た日々が ハートを輝かせている
The days I've gained are making my heart shine.
一人じゃないこと 気付かせてくれる
You make me realize that I'm not alone.
抱えきれぬほどの ありがとうの代わりに
In place of more 'thank yous' than I can hold,
鍵をかけて一つになる 受け止めて
locking it up and becoming one, accept it.
取り戻すんだ 光の未来 今 熱い想い
We'll take back the future of light, connecting our hot feelings now,
繋げ叶えにいくよ
we're going to make it come true.
君と一緒に願える軌跡重ねて
The miracle we can wish for together, layering,
広がっていくハーモニー 響け
and spreading, our harmony, let it ring out.
目覚める時がきたね
The time to wake up has come, hasn't it?
本当の自分になる
I'll become my true self.
満ちる運命
The destiny that fulfills.
取り戻したい 光の世界 その笑顔 勇気
I want to take back the world of light, that smile, courage,
涙 夢 希望の兆し
tears, dreams, the signs of hope.
君と明日を願う内からで生まれる
Our harmony, born from within as we wish for tomorrow with you,
私達のハーモニー 響け
let it ring out.
Yeah!
トライアングル・ドリーマー
Triangle Dreamer
デイ・バイ・デイ 日に日に募る乙女ゴコロ
Day by day, day after day, the feelings of a maiden grow stronger.
トライアングル・ドリーマー
Triangle Dreamer
#不知火フレア生誕祭2026
#ShiranuiFlareBirthday2026
Aクラスななめ　眩暈のおとなしい人
A-class, a tilt, a quiet person who makes me dizzy
カッコよくはない　だけど優しい
He's not cool, but he's kind
いつも頼れる彼
The guy I can always rely on
多角的恋愛相談の帰り道
On the way home from a multi-angled love consultation
なんだって話せる親友の女の子
My best friend girl I can talk to about anything
スポーツ万能　勉強もできて
She's good at sports and studying
女子力マックスです
And her girl power is at its max
どこにでもある　よくあること
It's a common thing that happens everywhere
急に彼女が
Suddenly, she said...
「あのね、実は私好きな人がいるの」って
"Hey, actually, there's someone I like"
ちょ、マジで！？
Wait, for real!?
三角形　三角形の恋は気まぐれ
Triangle, a triangle love is fickle
一瞬で　一瞬で崩れるバランス
In an instant, the balance collapses
ベタな漫画みたいなフラグ
A cliché manga-like flag
まさか自分も立てちゃうなんて残念すぎます
I can't believe I'm setting one up too, it's so unfortunate
三角形　三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, a triangle love is unstable
なんちゃって　なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
"Just kidding" isn't enough for this category
恋と友情　ゆらゆら揺れてなんか
Love and friendship, swaying back and forth
青春しちゃってます
I'm having a real youth moment
私、困っちゃってます
I'm in quite a bind
完敗です　お似合いすぎるわ　さてこんな日
A total loss, they suit each other too well. Now, on a day like this...
悔しいけど　どうかそんなんじゃなくて本心
It's frustrating, but please, I don't mean it that way, I'm being serious
っていうか既に応援モード　むしろ清々しい
Actually, I'm already in cheering mode, it's rather refreshing
だけど彼女は不思議な顔
But she has a mysterious look on her face
真剣な目で
With serious eyes...
「そうじゃなくて　私、あなたが　好き、ごめん」って
...she said, "No, I mean I like YOU, I'm sorry"
ちょ、マジで！？
Wait, for real!?
三角形　三角形の恋は気まぐれ
Triangle, a triangle love is fickle
一瞬で　一瞬で崩れるバランス
In an instant, the balance collapses
私、あなた、彼女と私
Me, you, her and me
超絶複雑　百合展開は想定外です
Extremely complex, a Yuri development was unexpected
三角形　三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, a triangle love is unstable
なんちゃって　なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
"Just kidding" isn't enough for this category
解けないパズル与え給うた神よ　恨んじゃいます
Oh God who gave me this unsolvable puzzle, I'll resent you
私、悩んじゃいます
I'm so troubled
あーもう！すごいヤバい！
Ah, jeez! This is so bad!
えっ、何！？　嬉しいけど、えっ、そういう意味じゃなくて！
Eh, what!? I'm happy but, eh, that's not what I meant!
だって、女の子同士だし…！　ねぇ、神様、どうしたらいいの！？
But, we're both girls...! Hey, God, what should I do!?
私、どうしたいの！？　ヘルプ・ミー！
What do I want to do!? Help me!
なんか変だ！愛に国境も、年も、性別も関係ない！
Something's strange! Love has no borders, age, or gender doesn't matter!
けど！けど！けど！
But! But! But!
三角形　三角形の恋は気まぐれ
Triangle, a triangle love is fickle
一瞬で　一瞬で崩れるバランス
In an instant, the balance collapses
普通の恋、夢見てたのになのに
I was dreaming of a normal love, and yet...
ノーマル捨てての私じゃちょっと無理ゲーすぎます
Abandoning my normal self is a bit too much of a "broken game" for me
三角形　三角形の恋は不安定
Triangle, a triangle love is unstable
なんちゃって　なんちゃってじゃ済まないカテゴリー
"Just kidding" isn't enough for this category
彼女のこと好きになれたらなんて妄想しちゃいます
I start to fantasize about if I could fall in love with her
私、おかしくなってます
I'm going crazy
PHOENIX PRAYER
煌々と　続く　ショートショート
Gleamingly, the short stories continue
喪失は　絶対デートって
Loss is an absolute date
今夜　輪廻　召喚　悲しみが
Tonight, reincarnation summons the sadness
混沌の　子守唄　歌ってるよ
A lullaby of chaos is being sung
運命に　理由が　あるのならば
If there's a reason for fate
全てを　懸けてみたいの
I want to try betting everything
あなたを　守りたい
I want to protect you
どこまでも　高く　飛べるわ
We can fly higher and higher
どこまでも　強く　なれるわ
We can become stronger and stronger
信じて　私に　出会えた奇跡
Believe in the miracle that led to our meeting
切り開くわ　不死鳥の　焔　解いて
I'll carve a path, unleashing the phoenix's flames
あなたの　側へ
To your side
Flap up, flap up
眼差し　焼きつかせるの
I'll burn your gaze into me
Flashback, flashback
振り解け　汗　挑み続けろ
Shake it off, the sweat, keep on challenging
飄々と　佇む　ホットショット
Aloofly, the hotshot stands
私が　必要でしょ
You need me, don't you?
今夜　輪廻　招待　正しさが
Tonight, an invitation to reincarnation, the righteousness...
ストレート　最前線に　押し出すよ
...will push you straight to the front lines
運命に　理由が　あるのならば
If there's a reason for fate
優しい　世界を　あげたい
I want to give you a gentle world
あなたを　包むわ
I'll wrap you up
どこまでも　早く　射抜くわ
Piercing through, faster and faster
どこまでも　熱く　焦がすわ
Burning hot, hotter and hotter
信じて　私に　出会えた奇跡
Believe in the miracle that led to our meeting
切り開くわ　不死鳥の　焔　解いて
I'll carve a path, unleashing the phoenix's flames
あなたの　側へ
To your side
Flap up, flap up
彼方越し　光を　見せて
Show me the light beyond the horizon
Flashback, flashback
許さない　情　進み続けろ
Unforgiving emotions, keep on advancing
尽きるまで　側にいると
I said I'd be by your side until the end
鼓動が　早くて　眩暈がする
My heart beats so fast, I feel dizzy
全て　捧げる
I'll offer everything
もう決めたの
I've already decided
最後の　チャンスだろ
It's the last chance, isn't it?
もう離さない
I'll never let go again
あなたに　燃ゆる
Burning for you
未来の風　跨がって行け
Ride the winds of the future
どこまでも　高く　飛べるわ
We can fly higher and higher
どこまでも　強く　なれるわ
We can become stronger and stronger
信じて　私に　出会えた奇跡
Believe in the miracle that led to our meeting
闇夜も　望めば　輝夜にするから
Even a dark night, if you wish, I'll turn it into a radiant one
切り開くわ　不死鳥の　焔　解いて
I'll carve a path, unleashing the phoenix's flames
あなたの　側へ
To your side
Flap up, flap up
眼差し　焼きつかせるの
I'll burn your gaze into me
Flashback, flashback
振り解け　汗　挑み続けろ
Shake it off, the sweat, keep on challenging
Flap up, flap up
彼方越し　光を　見せて
Show me the light beyond the horizon
Flashback, flashback
許さない　情　進み続けろ
Unforgiving emotions, keep on advancing
ダイアモンド クレバス
Diamond Crevasse
（ボーカル）
(Vocalizing)
神様に恋をしていた頃は
When I was in love with God,
こんな別れが来るとは思ってなかったよ
I never thought such a parting would come.
（ボーカル）
(Vocalizing)
もう二度と触れられないなら
If I can never touch you again,
せめて最後に もう一度抱きしめて欲しかったよ
I wanted you to hold me at least one last time.
It's long, long goodbye...
さよなら さよなら 何度だって
Goodbye, goodbye, no matter how many times
自分に無情に 言い聞かせて
I tell myself heartlessly,
手を振るのは優しさだよね
Waving my hand is an act of kindness, right?
今強さが欲しい
Now, I want strength.
あなたに出会い さあ輝いて
I met you, and now I'm shining,
私が生まれて
I was born,
愛すればこそ 愛あればこそ
Because I love you, because love exists,
希望のない奇跡を待って どうなるの？
What will happen if I wait for a miracle without hope?
涙に滲む 星の瞬きは…
The twinkling of the stars blurred by tears is...
忘れないよ あなたの温もりも
I won't forget your warmth,
その優しさも
Or that kindness,
すべて包んでくれた両手も
Or the hands that embraced everything.
It's long, long goodbye...
さよなら さよなら 愛しい人
Goodbye, goodbye, my beloved,
あなたがいたから 歩いて来れた
Because you were here, I was able to walk on.
一人なんかじゃなかったよね
I wasn't alone, was I?
今答えが欲しい
Now, I want an answer.
燃えるような流星 掴まえて 火を灯して
Catch a burning meteor and light a fire,
愛していたい 愛されていたい
I want to love, I want to be loved.
冷えた体 一つで世界はどうなるの？
With just one cold body, what will happen to the world?
張り続けてた虚勢が解けて…
The bluff I kept putting up melts away...
...Long Bow
どうしてだろう 涙溢れて
I wonder why, the tears overflow
止められない
I can't stop them.
あなたに出会い さあ輝いて
I met you, and now I'm shining,
私が生まれて
I was born,
愛すればこそ 愛あればこそ
Because I love you, because love exists,
希望のない奇跡を待って どうなるの？
What will happen if I wait for a miracle without hope?
涙に滲む 星の瞬きは…
The twinkling of the stars blurred by tears is...
もし生まれ変わって また巡り逢えるなら
If I'm reborn and we can meet again,
その時もきっと 私を見つけだして
Then, too, please find me.
もう二度と離さないで 掴まえてて
Never let me go again, hold on to me.
一人じゃないと
That I'm not alone
囁いてほしい プラネット
I want you to whisper, Planet
Paradise Lost
聖なる瞳が 痛みを映したら
When holy eyes reflect the pain
振り向いてごらん 情熱放つトリック
Turn around and see the trick that emits passion
崩れる足元 二人は戻れない
With the ground crumbling, the two of us can't go back
差し伸べた手をほどかないで
Don't let go of the hand I've reached out
消えるよまた 優しい日々が
Once again, the gentle days disappear
思い出を汚すのは許さない
I won't allow the memories to be defiled
ここは裏切りのティル・ナ・ノーグ
This is the Tir na nOg of betrayal
彷徨う心の果てに
At the end of a wandering heart
光を求めて 祈る言葉届けあなたに
Seeking light, may my prayerful words reach you
囚われの羽が 遥かな空へと向かう
Captured wings head toward the distant sky
信じたいよ私たち 孤独じゃない
I want to believe that we're not alone
分かり合える 絆の中で
We can understand each other within our bond
離さない 始まるデスティニー
I won't let go, the starting destiny
新たな願いに 鎖解ける時
When the chains are broken by a new wish
休ませてくれる 深い眠りに
Allow me to rest in a deep sleep
僅かな希望が 私を強くする
A faint hope makes me strong
ぬくもりに触れてみたいから
Because I want to try touching the warmth
蘇れば 儚き命
If it's resurrected, a fleeting life
繰り返す愛しさが導いた
Guided by the repeated affection
胸に泡沫の調べ 流れる世界の終わりに
A transient melody in my heart, at the end of a flowing world
諦めはしない 今がつなぐ明日探そう
I won't give up, let's find the tomorrow that 'now' connects
千切れ舞う羽は 未来の空にも向かう
The torn and dancing wings also head toward the future sky
忘れないで私たち 一つのクリスタル
Don't forget, we are a single crystal
輝いて 壊れないのよ
Shining, it won't break
離さない 誓いのデスティニー
I won't let go, the destiny of a vow
Lost Paradise...
消えるよまた 優しい日々が
Once again, the gentle days disappear
思い出を汚すのは許さない
I won't allow the memories to be defiled
ここは裏切りのティル・ナ・ノーグ
This is the Tir na nOg of betrayal
彷徨う心の果てに
At the end of a wandering heart
光を求めて 祈る言葉届けあなたに
Seeking light, may my prayerful words reach you
囚われの羽が 遥かな空へと向かう
Captured wings head toward the distant sky
信じたいよ私たち 孤独じゃない
I want to believe that we're not alone
分かり合える 絆の中で
We can understand each other within our bond
離さない
I won't let go
見つめて Paradise Lost
Stare at Paradise Lost
やっとみんな会えたね！
Finally we all met!
Nonstop No-stop The Finish!
GIRLS' LEGEND U
だって全力走りたい
Because I want to run at full speed
芝と砂と君の追い切りメニュー
Turf, dirt, and your final training menu
頼む頼む 声出せ叫べ
Please, please, raise your voice and shout
Whoa-oh-oh-oh
それぜ！ Fight! Oh! Fight! Oh!
That's it! Fight! Oh! Fight! Oh!
だって全力上がりたい
Because I want to rise at full speed
譲れない夢の途中
In the middle of an unyielding dream
始めよう ここから最高ストーリー
Let's begin, from here the best story
Whoa-oh-oh-oh...
あぁ 憧れに満ちて
Ah, filled with longing
語り合ったメモリー
Memories we talked about
もっとドキドキ もっとトキメキ
More pounding heart, more excitement
抑えられない たまんない
Can't hold it back, it's unbearable
熱いハラハラが止まらない
The hot suspense won't stop
君と 走り競いゴール目指し
With you, racing and aiming for the goal
はるか響け届けミュージック
Let the music resonate and reach far away
ずっとずっとずっとずっと想い
Always, always, always, always, these feelings
夢はきっと叶うなら
If the dream will surely come true
あの日君に感じた 何かを信じて
Believing in something I felt for you that day
春も夏も秋も冬も 越え願い焦がれ走れ
Crossing through spring, summer, autumn, winter, wishing, longing, and running
勝利へ！
To victory!
Nonstop No-stop The Finish!
だって全力弾けたい
Because I want to burst at full speed
大団円 決意 絆になった
The grand finale, determination, it became a bond
万丈 万丈 本気で叫べ
Banjou, banjou, shout in earnest
Whoa-oh-oh-oh
それぜ！ Fight! Oh! Fight! Oh!
That's it! Fight! Oh! Fight! Oh!
だって全力笑いたい
Because I want to laugh at full speed
最高峰 真ん中
Top peak, right in the center
リアルに ここから上昇ストーリー
Realistically, from here the rising story
Whoa-oh-oh-oh...
あぁ 駆け抜けた日々
Ah, days we ran through
語り合ったグローリー
Glory we talked about
今応えたい 生きてると
I want to answer now, that I'm alive
背中を押す声 熱くなれ
The voice pushing my back, become hot
夢は夢のまま 終われない
A dream can't end as just a dream
君と 未来描きゴール目指し
With you, drawing the future and aiming for the goal
狙い定め掴めウイニング
Set your aim and grab the winning
ずっとずっとずっとずっと想い
Always, always, always, always, these feelings
夢はきっと叶うから
Because the dream will surely come true
あの日君が鳴らした 涙も信じて
Believing even in the tears you shed that day
雨も風も雲も闇も 越え願い焦がれ走れ
Crossing through rain, wind, clouds, and darkness, wishing, longing, and running
勝利へ！
To victory!
揺るぎない覚悟決して
Never wavering resolve
一つ二つ共に綴る記録
One, two, records we write together
背中に迫る迷い振り払え
Shake off the hesitation closing in behind you
今の自分追い越すだけ
Just overtaking my current self
勝ちたい 勝ちたい 勝ちたい 君と勝ちたい！
I want to win, I want to win, I want to win, I want to win with you!
未来描きゴール目指し
Drawing the future and aiming for the goal
狙い定め掴めウイニング
Set your aim and grab the winning
ずっとずっとずっとずっと想い
Always, always, always, always, these feelings
夢はきっと叶うから
Because the dream will surely come true
あの日君が鳴らした 涙も信じて
Believing even in the tears you shed that day
春も夏も秋も冬も 越え 雨も風も越え
Crossing through spring, summer, autumn, winter, and rain and wind
雲も闇も越え 勝利へ！
Crossing through clouds and darkness, to victory!
キミと
With you
君と 走り競いゴール目指し
With you, racing and aiming for the goal
はるか響け届けミュージック
Let the music resonate and reach far away
ずっとずっとずっとずっと想い
Always, always, always, always, these feelings
夢はきっと叶うから
Because the dream will surely come true
あの日君に感じた 何かを信じて
Believing in something I felt for you that day
春も夏も秋も冬も 越え願い焦がれ走れ
Crossing through spring, summer, autumn, winter, wishing, longing, and running
勝利へ！
To victory!
夏も秋も冬も越え 願え 焦がれ 走れ
Transcending summer, autumn, and winter, wish, yearn, and run
Ah 勝利へ
Ah, towards victory
未来 描き 彩 目指し 狙い 挑め つかめ Winning
Drawing the future, coloring it, aiming, challenging, and seizing victory
ずっとずっとずっと想い 夢はきっと叶うから
Holding onto this feeling forever, because dreams will surely come true
あの日に君が流した 涙も信じて
Believe even in the tears you shed that day
雨も風も雲も闇も越え 願え 焦がれ 走れ
Transcending rain, wind, clouds, and darkness, wish, yearn, and run
Ah 勝利へ
Ah, towards victory
Non-stop! Non-stop to finish!
STARTING OVER
It's finally the true end
I'm ready for... my destiny
I'm ready for... STARTING OVER
やっと幕を下ろせた 最後の瞬間まで
I was finally able to lower the curtain until the final moment
わたしは精一杯に わたしをやりきった
I did my best to be myself to the fullest
終演の続きは 誰も知らなくていい
No one needs to know what happens after the show ends
涙を置いて 新しい旅に出よう
Leave the tears behind and set out on a new journey
熱狂はあなたを選ぶ 違う結末だっただけ
The enthusiasm chose you, it was just a different ending
同じ愛になれなかった Destiny
Destiny that couldn't become the same love
これまでの全てを 差し出すような愛だった
It was a love that seemed to give up everything until now
世界の意味が変わるくらいに 肯定された気がしたんだ
I felt so affirmed that it was as if the meaning of the world had changed
何気なさの中で 気づけた最初の奇跡が
The first miracle I noticed in the midst of casualness
あなたでよかった わたしでよかった 心から思えたよ
I'm glad it was you, I'm glad it was me, I felt that from the bottom of my heart
ずっと遠い未来も ちゃんと覚えていよう
Let's remember properly even in the far-off future
自分の抱きしめかた 明日の願いかた
How to embrace myself, how to wish for tomorrow
あなたがいなくても わたしの片隅で
Even if you are not here, in a corner of my heart
優しい光 消えたりしないとわかる
I know the gentle light will not fade away
今はまだ手を振れるほど 道は別れたばかりで
I can still wave my hand, the paths have only just parted
後ろ髪に風を感じながら
While feeling the wind in my hair from behind
それまでの全てが あなたに出会うためだった
Everything until then was to meet you
どの瞬間もムダじゃないこと 本当の意味で知れたから
Because I learned in the true sense that no moment is wasted
次の曲がり角も 自分らしさで選べるはず
I should be able to choose the next corner as myself
いつかに繋がる 新しい一歩 信じて歩き出そう
Let's believe and start walking a new step that leads to sometime
心から誰かを愛せた あの日々は
Those days when I could love someone from the bottom of my heart
間違いなくわたしの Destiny Ah
Are definitely my destiny, ah
これまでの全てが 新しい力をくれる
Everything until now gives me new strength
どの瞬間もムダじゃないなら 何が起きても大丈夫だから
If no moment is wasted, then everything will be alright no matter what happens
次の物語も 自分らしさで選べるはず
I should be able to choose the next story as myself
いつかに繋がる わたしのはじまり 信じて歩き出そう
Let's believe and start walking my beginning that leads to sometime
いつか繋がる　わたしのはじまり
Someday they'll connect, my beginning
信じて歩き出そう
Believe and start walking forward
再び幕は上がる
The curtain rises once again
聴いていただいたのは新曲の「STARTING OVER」でした！
That was my new song, "STARTING OVER"!
はい、新年一発目、新曲の初披露というわけで...
Yes, to start the new year, it was the first performance of my new song...
ぬるっとね、新曲をやってしまったんですが...
I just sort of slipped the new song in there...
平成感のある、懐かしみの感じの楽曲をこちらですね、歌わせていただいたんですけれども...
I sang this song which has a nostalgic, Heisei-era feel to it...
この後、この曲が24時から、あと数時間後か。
After this, at 24:00—just a few hours from now.
24時からですね、1月30日の24時から配信、リリースされます。
Starting at 24:00 on January 30th, it will be released on streaming services.
たくさん聴いてください！今年もね、たくさんオリ曲出していきたいです！
Please listen to it a lot! I want to release many original songs this year too!
そしてそして、もうMCがね、実は最後なのでね、えーと...
And then, this is actually the last MC section...
この配信の後にはメンバー限定の配信もあるので、よろしくお願いします。
After this stream, there'll be a members-only stream, so please look forward to that.
よしよしよし、グッズ紹介！えー、ここには同期のねぽらぼを大集合ということで...
Alright, alright, alright, time for the goods introduction! I'm bringing my gen-mates NePolabo together here...
ね、ら、ぼ、集まれー！
Nene, Lamy, Botan, get over here!
イエーイ！きたー！
Yay! We're here!
はい、ちゃちゃちゃちゃ、初めて呼ばれました、どうも。
Yes, ta-da! I've been called for the first time. Hello.
あれ、初だっけ？
Wait, is this the first time?
ポルカチャンネル初でーす！
First time on Polka's channel!
ポルカチャンネル誕生日、誕生日おめでとう！
Happy birthday on Polka's channel!
おめでとうー！
Happy birthday!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
ここまでが流れでございます、はい。
That's the planned flow, yes.
ずっと待ってたから！待ってた、待ってた！
We've been waiting! Waiting and waiting!
グッズをね、紹介させていただきたいと思います。
I'd like to introduce the goods now.
合間ながらのリアクションなど各々取っていただけると嬉しいです。
I'd love it if you all could react along as we go.
ガヤガヤー！
Reactions, reactions!
というわけで、尾丸ポルカ誕生日記念グッズ2026、ラインナップはこちら！
So, here's the lineup for Omaru Polka Birthday Celebration Goods 2026!
ドン！ドン！
Tada!
というわけで、素晴らしい今回もラインナップが揃っております。
As you can see, we have another wonderful lineup this time.
あれ？すごいけど、なんかちょっと盛ってません？
Wait. It's great, but aren't things a bit... exaggerated?
盛ってませんよ！盛ってません！
They're not exaggerated! I didn't exaggerate!
というわけで、まず一つずつ紹介していきましょう。まずは、こちら！
So, let's introduce them one by one. First, this!
はい。ポルカのはじめての抱き枕カバーになっております。
Yes. It's Polka's first-ever body pillow cover.
おおー！すごい！かわいい！
Ooh! Amazing! So cute!
エッ、ポルカ、ちょっと、パンツ履いてません？
Wait, Polka... aren't you not wearing any panties?
あれ？丸出しじゃないですか？
Wait, are you completely exposed?
履いてます！そんな部屋着だよ！
I'm wearing them! It's just loungewear!
部屋着！だって、ねねだって、こういう部屋着だろ？
It's loungewear! Nene, you wear stuff like this too, right?
わちゃわちゃ、ちょっと。ステイ、ステイ！人のチャンネルだからってやりたい放題チャンネルして！
Hey, hey, hold on! Stay, stay! Don't just do whatever you want on someone else's channel!
シャツで寝たらシワつくぞ！
If you sleep in a shirt like that, it'll get wrinkled!
お、まじレス！まじレス！写真撮影用かもしれないです！
Oh, a serious reply! That's a literal response! It might just be for the photo shoot!
というわけで、はじめて抱き枕カバー出します。表が通常衣装で...
So, I'm releasing my first body pillow cover. The front is my usual outfit...
...裏は彼シャツになってます！
...and the back is the boyfriend shirt!
彼シャツ！彼シャツいいですねー！
Boyfriend shirt! I love the boyfriend shirt!
はい、ありがとうございます、皆さん。パセリ先生ありがとう！
Yes, thank you everyone. Thank you, Paseri-sensei!
続きまして、ドン！
Moving on... Tada!
こちら、歴代衣装のポルカランダムラバーストラップです！
Here are the Polka Random Rubber Straps featuring past outfits!
かわいいー！
So cute!
これまでの衣装のラバーストラップ、こちら、のいみね先生に描いていただきました！
These rubber straps of my past outfits were illustrated by Noimine-sensei!
えー、めっちゃいいじゃん、これ！
Whoa, these are really good!
どの衣装が出るかお楽しみに。ありがとう、みんなリアクション本当に100点満点です！
Look forward to seeing which outfit you get. Thanks, everyone's reactions are perfect!
はい、続きまして、こちら！
Okay, next is this!
ドン！どれもこれも宝物思い出バインダー！
Tada! The "Every Single One Is a Treasure" Memory Binder!
おお、いいね！かわいい！
Oh, nice! It's cute!
これですね、最近みんな特典でチェキ風ブロマイドカード出したりしてるから、そういうの入れられたり...
Since everyone's been releasing polaroid-style cards as bonuses lately, you can put those in here...
...あとはホロカも入るサイズになっておりますので、ぜひぜひいろんな思い出しまってください。
...and it's also sized for Hololive Official Cards, so please use it to store all your memories.
いいですねー！しまってください！
That's good! Store them away!
はい、そして続きましては、こちら！
And next is this!
ポルカのしっぽキーホルダー！
Polka's Tail Keychain!
えー！かわいい！
Oh! Cute!
一周して流行ってるからね、ポルカのしっぽ型のキーホルダー。
They've come back into style, you know? A keychain shaped like Polka's tail.
そう、平成レトロみたいな感じで出ております。
Yeah, it's being released with a Heisei-retro kind of vibe.
確かに、平成レトロみたいな感じ。
True, it does feel Heisei-retro.
はい、こちらもつけてください。
Please wear this one too.
そして、ボイスも出ます。ボイスはこちら。ジャン！ASMRボイスです。
And there's a voice pack too. Here it is. Ta-da! An ASMR voice pack.
おおー！
Ooh!
はい、えーと、ま、「彼シャツポルカの、ただいまの抱擁」というね、ちょっとタイトルもなんか...
Yes, well, it's titled "Boyfriend Shirt Polka's 'Welcome Home' Hug," so the title is a bit...
狙ってるじゃん！てぇてぇ、天下！
You're totally aiming for it! So wholesome! Top tier!
やめてよー、もう！天下天下！なんで今日同期呼んじゃったんだろうって一瞬思った、今。恥ずかしくなってきた。
Stop it! Top tier, my foot! I just had a moment where I wondered why I invited my gen-mates today. I'm getting embarrassed.
勝ち！くぅー！
We win! Whew!
えっと、添い寝ASMRというか抱き枕カバーとイラストの関係があるシナリオになってます。
Anyway, it's a sleeping-together ASMR, with a scenario linked to the body pillow cover illustration.
おおー！
Ooh!
お待たせしました、フルセット購入特典になっております。こちら。
Thanks for waiting, here's the Full Set Purchase Bonus. This.
チェキ風ブロマイドカード！数量限定が直筆メッセージ、箔押し複製サインになっております。
A polaroid-style card! The limited quantity version includes a handwritten message and a foil-stamped signature.
おおー、いいな！
Ooh, nice!
通常が箔押し複製サインとメッセージ入りでございます。
The regular version comes with a foil-stamped signature and a printed message.
フルセットぜひぜひ買っていただいた方には、特典ボイスとして...
For those who buy the Full Set, as a bonus voice...
...「すやすやポルカの、いちばん熱い約束」という添い寝ボイスというか...
...the sleeping-together voice pack titled "Sleeping Polka's Dearest Promise"...
「一緒にね、寝ようね」みたいな感じのなんかちょっと...
Something like "Let's sleep together," and it's a bit of a...
添い寝ボイスになってて、
...co-sleeping voice,
こっちもASMRになってます。
and this one is also ASMR.
おおー。
Ooh.
よろしくお願いします。
Please look forward to it.
恥ずかしいなあ、みんなとやるのこれ。
It's embarrassing doing this with everyone.
なんか、エッチな女になってしまった。
I've become some kind of sexy woman.
すいません。
I'm sorry.
いいじゃない。新年もね、皆さん改めてこれからよろしくお願いします。
It's fine. It's a new year, and we look forward to working with you again.
よろしくお願いします。
We look forward to it.
というわけでね、今日はみんなで最後一緒に歌うために呼んできたということで、
So, I invited everyone here today to sing together for the finale,
準備してきました！
and we're all ready!
行きますよ！
Here we go!
せーの！
Ready, go!
準備おっけー！
Ready to go!
脚本は捨てちゃおうか
Let's throw away the script
差し当たり焼き付けよ
For now, let's burn it in
アドリブの熱いパフォーマンス
An ad-lib hot performance
屋根裏を飛び出して
Jump out of the attic
壮大なステージに響く
Resonating on the grand stage
特別なストーリー
A special story
瞼の裏には虹が架く
A rainbow forms behind the eyelids
星空のメモリー
Memories of the starry sky
等身大の愛を込めて
With full-sized love
想像を超える世界へ
To a world beyond imagination
誰も知らないでしょう
Nobody knows, right?
Are You ready?
どんな未来か見に行こうよ
Let's go see what kind of future it is
なんて自由だ 笑っちゃうよね
How free, it's almost laughable, right?
ねえ ホログラムよりも先へ
Look, further than the hologram
誰だって置いてかないよ
I won't leave anyone behind
ごらん 歓声が呼んでいる
Look, the cheers are calling
ステップからパッと照らす
Flashily illuminating from the step
人生のスポットライト
The spotlight of life
薔薇色のプレミアンショー
A rose-colored premium show
ここが特等席よ
This is the special seat
街灯は手拍子より
Streetlights are better than handclaps
天気次第のエチュード
An étude depending on the weather
まるで物語
Just like a story
捕まえてよ
Catch me
待って ほら
Wait, look
予想のできない展開に
In an unpredictable development
ステージは揺れる
The stage is shaking
特別なストーリー
A special story
耳を澄ましたら
If you listen closely
月が踊る
The moon dances
雨音のハーモニー
Harmony of the sound of rain
浮かぶ ふわふわな空想
Floating, fluffy fantasy
暴走 底なしの本能
Out of control, bottomless instinct
すべて知りたでしょう
You want to know everything, right?
Hey guys! 叫べ 気分は最高
Hey guys! Shout out! The mood is the best
最高！
Highest!
Come on! もっと叫べ 気分は最高
Come on! Shout out even more! The mood is the best
最高！
Highest!
ポルカ終わるか？
Will Polka end?
終わらない！
It won't end!
It's showtime!
繋いだ手 離さないでなんてね
Don't let go of the hand we held, just kidding
どうしたって 重たくなっちゃって困るわ
No matter what, it gets heavy and I'm troubled
いつの日か エピローグを一緒に綴ろう
Let's write the epilogue together someday
きっと約束よ
It's a promise, for sure
Life goes on!
どんな未来か見に行こうよ
Let's go see what kind of future it is
なんて自由だ 笑っちゃうよね
How free, it's almost laughable, right?
ねえ ホログラムよりも先へ
Look, further than the hologram
夢のような 花舞台に感情を馳せたら
If you let your emotions run free on the dream-like flower stage
ステップからパッと照らす
Flashily illuminating from the step
人生のスポットライト
The spotlight of life
薔薇色のプレミアンショー
A rose-colored premium show
どこへだって添い遂げたい
I want to stay with you wherever we go
ここが特等席よ
This is the special seat
出演：尾丸ポルカ
Cast: Omaru Polka
AZKi
百鬼あやめ
Nakiri Ayame
あんたにゃ　もうもったいない
He's just not good enough for you
大神ミオ
Ookami Mio
不知火フレア
Shiranui Flare
あたしゃ　ほんと ナイスバディ　バディ　バディ
I really have a nice body, body, body
宝鐘マリン
Houshou Marine
自分で言うくらい
Even if I say so myself
桃鈴ねね
Momosuzu Nene
タダじゃない じゃない じゃない じゃない！
I'm not cheap, not cheap, not cheap, not cheap!
雪花ラミィ
Yukihana Lamy
あけっぴろげに　しゃべれば
If you speak openly
獅白ぼたん
Shishiro Botan
寂しけりゃ　エブリバディ　バディ　バディ
If you're lonely, everybody, body, body
鷹嶺ルイ
Takane Lui
誰にも判らない
Nobody knows
風真いろは
Kazama Iroha
恋愛って　いつ火がつくのか
When it comes to love, who knows when the spark will fly?
座員くん
Zain-kun
ダイナマイト
Dynamite
開拓者
Kaitakusha
恋はダイナマイト
Love is dynamite
ぽよ余
Poyoyo
ミオファ
Miofa
どんなに不景気だって　恋はインフレーション
No matter how bad the recession, love is inflation
がんも つくね つみれ
Ganmo, Tsukune, Tsumire
ぽこべぇ
Pokobe
バックダンサーズ
Back Dancers
こんなに優しくされちゃ　みだら
Being treated so kindly makes me feel... naughty
明るい未来に　就職希望だわ
I hope to get a job in a bright future
日本の未来は
Japan's future is...
世界がうらやむ
...the envy of the world
恋をしようじゃないか
Shall we fall in love?
Wow wow wow wow Dance! Dancin' all of the night!
なんだか　物足りない
Something feels missing
どこにいたって　愛してほしいわ
No matter where I am, I want you to love me
自分で伝えるの
I'll tell you myself
恥ずかしくない ない ない
I'm not embarrassed, not at all, not at all!
いっそのこと　二人で
Might as well, the two of us
憧れよ　エブリバディ　バディ　バディ
Aspire to it, everybody, body, body
誰しも気づいてない
Nobody has noticed yet
恋愛って　ゆめの落とし穴
Love is a dream's trap
ミステリー
Mystery
恋はミステリー
Love is a mystery
寸前の不自然だって　恋のインサイダー
Even an unnatural moment before, love's an insider
それでも上手にされちゃ　あらわ
Even so, being handled so well leaves me exposed
幸せ　来る日も　キャンセル待ちなの
Happiness is on a cancellation waiting list, day after day
あんたの笑顔は
Your smile is...
世界がうらやむ
...the envy of the world
夢があるじゃないか
There's a dream, isn't there?
Wow wow wow wow Dance! Dancin' all of the night!
Love love love machine
Love love love station
Love love love factory
Love love is so wonderful
Yeah!
日本の未来は
Japan's future is...
世界がうらやむ
...the envy of the world
恋をしようじゃないか
Shall we fall in love?
Wow wow wow wow Dance! Dancin' all of the night!
座員のみんなも
Everyone in the troupe too
あんたもあたしも
You and I too
みんなも社長さんも
Everyone and even the CEOs
Wow wow wow wow Dance! Dancin' all of the night!
LOVEマシーン！
LOVE Machine!
今日は主役だ！！ まだまだかがやく場所へつれていくぜ！！ I LOVE YOU ♡ 2026.1.30 Polka
Today I'm the star!! I'll take you to even more shining places!! I LOVE YOU ♡ 2026.1.30 Polka
新曲のお披露目あり！ Glitter Love 1/30 21:00 ~ ポルカのライブ過去最多 ホロメンゲスト 10名
New song reveal! Glitter Love 1/30 21:00 ~ Polka's live with the most Hololive guests ever: 10 people
#尾丸ポルカ生誕祭2026
新曲のお披露目あり！
Glitter Love
#OmaruPolkaBirthday2026
New song reveal!
Glitter Love
1/30 21:00~
ポルカのライブ過去最多 ホロメンゲスト10名
Most guests in Polka's live history: 10 hololive members